millionairex5.com 2015-06-11

# .: MX500 - 50 weekly MLM POWER audios and the opportunity to earn USD500 again and again and again... - MX500 Privacy Policy :.

**> > MX500 Privacy Policy <<**

MX500 is the only operator collecting or maintaining personal information through the www.millionairex5.com website.

We at 

MX500 Corporate are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information or data that we collect about you lawfully and ethically.

By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy whenever you visit this website to make sure that you understand how any personal data you provide will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this Privacy Policy are for this website only. If you link to other websites, please review the Privacy Policy posted at those websites.

**COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION**

We at 

MX500 Corporate collect personally identifiable data, like names and email addresses, when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The data you provide is used to fulfill your specific request for information about the MX500 business. Aside from the information found in this website, we do send further information and updates via email, that's why we ask for your name and email address.

Unless you have given us your consent, we shall not send any type of email message to you except that which is related to your request, which is information about the 

MX500 program.

**TRACKING ACTIVITY**

We at 

MX500 Corporate may use technology to track the patterns of behavior of visitors to our website. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this from happening.

**DISTRIBUTION OF INFORMATION**

We at 

MX500 Corporate may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

**COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure on a secure server protected by password and firewall. Only authorized corporate staff of 

MX500 have access to this information.

The names and email addresses collected are not sold, or disclosed to any third parties.

You have the choice to stop receiving further emails from 

MX500 by clicking on the 'Unsubscribe' link at the lower part of any of our messages to you. Alternately you may send an email to MX500 Admin with the word “UNSUBSCRIBE” at your discretion.

**PRIVACY CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below:

  **MX500 REGISTERED OFFICE**

MillionaireX7 Global Incorporated  
Mill Mall Tower, 2nd Floor  
Wickhams Cay 1  
Road Town  
Tortola  
British Virgin Islands 1110  
Telephone: +63-939-253-3333  
Email: [admin@millionairex5.com](mailto:admin@millionairex5.com)

Note: This policy document along with all policy documents within our website must be reviewed and approved prior to use for your particular purpose. No statement of legality or compliance with any regulatory agencies is made in providing you with this document.
